Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â
This program is a variety show where Ana-chan tries various things!
Let's go next.
In symbols
The best
When I liked rice cakes.
what is that?
is, of course, the prevailing law.
Hey, there are already 20 circles all over the place!
That didn't matter much earlier.
Kano-chan usually has a lot of intuition about what's going on?
Real Silence.
Real Silence is the 10th favorite at 32.5 times.
The 10th favorite?
I don't believe it.
What do you mean, it's that low?
Yeah.
And the most popular?
Most popular.
When I liked mochi.
1.5 times.
If we did 10,000 yen, it would be 15,000 yen.
That's low.
That's why I'm going to make a trifecta with the rice cake lover's time as the first place.
When it's born
To be honest, I don't have a lot of money.
Really? No?
No, I'll spend it.
Spend it on what?
But it's gone before you know it.
So 100,000 is a lot of money, then, isn't it?
You bought a lot of things, didn't you?
That's right. 100,000 is a lot.
If I win this, it'll make up for what I just said.
That's right.
I'll just win the first place prize.
If I want to make up the 20,000 yen I just spent...
I'd have to spend 40,000 yen.
That's 1.5 times the price.
Okay, then.
40,000? That much?
Did you see that? You know what I saw?
The most popular guy comes in second.
That's right.
When you're the favorite, it doesn't matter if you finish first or second.
And then you guess the pair that comes in first or second again.
You know, there's something to be said for guessing which pair will finish first or second again.
When you like to keep it, it's on the axis.
36 like this is 8 times 37, so you can choose any one of them, and the other one is definitely not this one, but
Tremblant or Miner Global.
Is that so?
But if I win either one...
Yes, really.
I don't want to be like that anymore.
Shouldn't we put insurance on it?
I don't need insurance.
That's cool.
I wonder how we'd change it if we did that.
Triple single.
I think a single trifecta might be a little too low-priced.
That's why we're going with the single.
So we'll go with the single?
So Real Silence.
Oh, Real Silence... 20 times.
Oh, and I get 20,000 back.
I'm gonna get 20,000 back, and it's gonna be 1,000 yen.
That's great.
Can I buy two single tickets?
Not at all.
I'm talking about the single win, I'm hungry.
That's fine, too.
I'll get more for my money.
More?
What?
Only if you don't come in first.
You can't do that, asshole.
Linkage.
Linkage?
Transaction.
Infe Soleil looks strong.
Okay, 8x, 8x, 9x.
That's what I'm talking about. Even if we win with 3, we'll still have a former trend, someone's coming.
Okay, Linkage.
Just linkages?
Yeah, I'm sure.
How much for the linkage?
30,000.
It'll be 25,000 to 60,000 when they get here.
You want to do that?
Yeah, I do.
And why is that, by the way?
Because it's a little loud.
Is that it? I like it.
You look like you're having fun.
What do you want?
I think I'll go with the one from when I liked rice cakes.
Most popular.
I don't know how much.
Well, I...
10,000 yen.I'll give you 10,000 yen.
What's the matter?
Why don't you put a lot of money on it?
Eight times as much.
I don't mind if it's a little less.
I see what you're getting at.
I want my 100,000 back.
I want 100,000 back.
Okay, a little less than 10,000.
Twelve thousand.
I'll give you one.
I'll make it 100 yen.
One time.
Okay.
[fast forward]
Well, well, well. We'll see how it goes.
Yes, for now.
Move, move, move!
Hey, Gull, what's wrong with you?
[fast forward]
We've been on the lam.
This whole day...
Hey...
[fast forward]
All right.
Okay, so it's big protection time.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I had infinite time earlier, so...
[fast forward]
Please.
Give me a hand.
A lot of kids watch this show.
Oh, I dropped it.
I'm spinning.
I'm telling you, it was totally unintentional.
Kids, hand spinners...
It's gonna hit.
Of course it's going to hit you.
You're not very good at this.
Oh, wow.
Why is it 1400? Why is it shorter than before?
This reminds me of when I ran track and field.
I remember when I ran relays and half-distance races.
It makes me nervous.
Did you run in competitions?
I was.
I was in one level.
It's like, "Yo, Don!
I'm scared to start.
Here it comes.
It's starting! Where'd you go? Where's the good luck charm?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Oh, yeah.
Because that's where we're going to end up.
It's starting. It's starting.
It's started. - It's started where?
Oh, here it comes.
And then we go around like this.
You're looking good.
Where is it?
You're right, you're right, you're right.
Do me a favor.
Three, three, three, now three.
Number three, number three.
I'm so happy.
But something doesn't look right.
It's no good.
What's that?
It's a little far back.
Come on.
But in horse racing, it doesn't really matter where you are at the moment.
When he goes down the last straight, he's going to make a big move right in front of you, and that's where you're going to be.
There he is.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Wow, Cammon, that's great.
Good luck.
Where's my car?
Your car?
You're coming back from the service area.
I was standing in line in the parking lot, and you...
Car. No, no, no, no.
Horse, horse, horse, horse.
First place, first place.
First place.
You're in first place after all.
It was one after all.
One hundred yen.
What about me?
That's a lot for 100 yen.
It was only 150 yen for 100 yen.
Well, I guess we're not going to make any more enemies.
I spent a lot of money.
I see.
She's got good taste.
She's so charismatic. I thought she was supposed to win these things.
So far, she hasn't won a single race.
Don't worry. There are two more races.Don't worry, there's two more races.
I just need a little help.
Oh, God.
Oh, I'm getting more and more like that at the racetracks.
Oh, yeah?
I'm a scruffy old man.
Oh, really?
That's what I'm talking about.
So, what do you want to do about race three?
But I've got 20 pick pokers.
1.3 times.
1.3?
So we're just gonna have to take all of them?
Well, well, well, well.
I'll put 68,000 on it.
No, you're spending too much.
Why not? But it's too low.
But, I mean, if we put 68,000 on it, we'd never make the fourth race.
Okay, 60,000.
Pick poker.
Okay, four.
You put 60,000 on me, I only get 18,000 back.
How's that? That's...
It's 1.3x.
How's that? It's not bad, is it?
Pick a poker demon and another one.
That's a good one.
What do you think?
You know what? It's a one-time deal, so why don't you make it a hundred yen?
That's fine.
I don't have much time.
All right, all right.
I'll give you 100 yen for the pick poker game.
All right.
I'll do it.
OK. - OK.
All right, well, I'll buy it.
For now.
Here's the receipt.
All right. - All right.
I'll get one.
We each bought one of these.
The same one.
Same one.
So let's just try this one and see how it goes.
That's fine.
I know you're gonna do this, but...
It's got to go somewhere.
I'll put it on.
I don't know.
I'll put it on the button.
Nice purple.
Yeah. - Okay.
Okay, okay.
Oh, that's good.
It's gonna be a lot more powerful now, right?
It'll go up. Heart, heart, heart.
All right.
Come on.
Come on, Big Boker.
Give me the Big Boker.
What's the number again?
Yellow five.
It's starting.
Huh.
All together at the 12-horse gate.
Uh-oh.
How's it going?
Mmm-hmm.
What's with the white mask, Big Boooker?
No?
No.
After that.
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
Little by little, Big Boooker, little by little.
Little by little, he's pulling ahead.
Coming up on turns three and four.
Third position alone, sixth position, Prevalence.
Fourth, also pulling away.
And here comes Big Booker, number 5 on the day. His mouth is going to fly open and he's going to show number 10, Big Booker, and then he'll be in the winner's circle, number 12.
And then we'll go straight from the top to number 12, Joyful Label, number 3.
I've got a lot of recruits, so I'm going to try a little harder and get them all going.
Boober.
You know what I'm talking about?
I like you... you're adopted.
Here he comes!
Ta-da!
Are you happy?
Yeah, I'm happy.
You don't think we should've spent 60,000 on it?
Yeah, you should have.
Masa.
Ehhhh...
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
We should've spent 60,000!
You should've spent it.
Why?
You're not coming back.
It's 1.3 or 1.5 times as much.It's 1.3 times or 1.5 times that much.
Okay, next.
Last but not least, Ron Race.
There's only seven of us.
There's only seven of them.
Happy ending. I bet he's cute.
It's a happy ending.
But I'm pretty sure it's a real girly thing.
Just in case.
It's easier to win when there's fewer of them.
It's easy to win.
But the odds are low
But some people call them declared tops.
Because the odds are so high.
Twenty-two times.
That's why the first place is
Declared Top
Second place, happy ending.
See, let's go from lowest to highest, in order of rank.
Geez!
No, if it comes like that...
No, I don't know.
Because the higher the och is, the better
It's easier anyway.
40 times that.
There's 2.4 million.
What about realgar?
No? I'll put realgar in there, I promise.
Oh, you want Real Gir? Because it's the most popular.
Even the trifecta.
All of them, without the pictures.
Just the trifecta.
That's good.
I don't even know what it is.
It's all right.
We'll see who wins the first place. Triple Crown.
Oh, that's why it's realgar, isn't it?
First place.
Oh, no? What do you think?
What? Who was that guy who just won?
Was it Pocahontas?
Pocahontas?
He was the most popular guy and he won first place.
So did Realgar.
So you're going to be the favorite to win the top prize?
Who's the favorite? The second and third place finishers.
I don't care what you pick.
Take two.
You can pick three and four.
I like your guess on this one.
I don't care who wins.
Honestly, it doesn't matter.
Yeah, I know.
Happy ending and a declared top.
Oh.
Who's Mazao?
It's not a boy.
Mazao.
Mazao. He's the most popular boy.
So...
We should put Mazao in there.
Mazao?
Mazao.
Flake.
You want to put Mazao in? This one too.
All together.
Twelve ways.
Multiply by 40, 69...
30 times 19.
If we go for 5,000 yen each...
For example.
If you multiply by 70
350,000.
Okay?
You're okay with the lineup?
Yeah. - Okay.
One of them's a real golfer.
Second and third place.
The second and third are the other four you just picked out.
Someone else...
You want to buy them together?
That's fine.
We just won the same one.
We have the same good luck charm.
Let's buy one together.
A good-luck charm.
Nice!
We'll go with this.
I'll spend 67,200.
Great.
I'll spend 79,200 yen.
For life.
You're going to win. I'm serious.
You're gonna win.
I'm going to have to ask my good luck charm to do something for me.
Don't play with me.
If I don't show up, it's over.
Real is the best.
Real is definitely number one.
You're the one who's predicting that everybody's gonna come in first.Who all expect to be in first place.
That's why I put it in there.
Please, really.
I don't know why.
It's so frustrating.
Shibuya City?
You're doing this for no money?
And then you run out of money?
And then you'll do it?
And then you lose it?
Well, I feel sorry for you.
Poor me, right?
I mean...
The more I think about it, the more I feel sorry for him.
All I want to do is race.
I just want to go to the races, and then I lose all my money.
I lose all my money.
And then I do it again and lose more money.
And then I do it again, because I want to do it.
And then I lost it all.
I feel sorry for you.
And everyone hates me.
What does that have to do with anything? Horse racing.
No, it doesn't.
I'm losing it... as a person.
Everyone hates me.
And in Kanto.
You mean the Kanto foreskin?
I've never heard a woman say that in Kanto.
I even have a foreskin.
You feel sorry for him, don't you?
I feel so sorry for you.
Let's all be nice to him.
They hate me so much.
That's a high grade.
But I hope I win this.
You hope I win? It's gonna win.
I hope I win.
Thank you, Smurf.
What do you mean?
You like horse racing, don't you, Smap?
What did you say, Mori?
I wonder if I'll win!
It's a game with a lever that never fails.
That's great!
You're the winner!
What are you talking about?
We won the fucking thing.
You remember.
I've got your good luck charm.
Take the good luck charm.
I don't think I can do this anymore.
I've only got the seventh prize, so you're going to win it for real.
The real gurus are coming.
First one's number 5.
Here we go.
Dovalgar!
Real Garfield.
Where's Realgar?
The yellow hat.
Yellow-green hat.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Real gurl's coming in one by one.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, please.
Please, please, please, please.
A little more. A little more.
Please, please, please.
No, from here, from here, from here.
What's that? Best day ever. Number five.
Real life's at the bottom. Now.
Huh?
What? Why?
What?
No, not quite. Not quite. From here to there. From here to there.
From here, from here, from here
What the hell!
What? Doval's in last place.
No, why are we in last place?
No way!
He's really the best.
Why?
He's in last place.
Really?
I can't stand it.
What? They said we were that good?
They're pissed.
Get out of here.
Oh, God.
I'm done.
I'm leaving. I'm leaving. I'm leaving.
I'm going home.
You lost 100,000.
Yes, sir.
You know, I lost 100,000 on my first horse race.
The only winning ticket was 100 yen.
Hmm...
I thought you were supposed to win this kind of thing.Aren't these things right?
I'm sure you'll be right about these.
That's me.
Don't underestimate me.
The most popular, the least popular...
No way.
So it's your curse.
But it'll be fun to find out.
I want revenge
I want revenge.
If we keep going like this.
Let's get revenge.
What do you want to do next?
I mean something different. What do you want to do?
Next time, we'll make a pact.
You should look forward to it.
That's the spirit.
Agreement. Next.
Me.
He says he feels like he could be somebody.